Hey, John.
Hey, Sam. What's going on? Doing great.
Where are you calling from? Sam,
Nigeria.
From where? Nigeria.
Oh, what's up, Sam? Oh, it's you. Yeah.
Good to, uh, good to hear from you, man.
Thank. How's, um, how's everything going on your end?
Doing great. I have a lot of, lots of work to do.
I have only one week break for
season, so I have lots of work on my hands.
Oh, you're busy is cool because of the holidays. Yeah,
Yeah. Because of the
holidays. Yeah.
Do you have, how many clients do you have?
Well, I was working with three clients
and I, I dropped one last month.
Mm-Hmm. Two clients.
So are you full-time with them?
Yeah, I'm Nice. That's good.
Have you, um, have you gotten any clients
from the community?
No. No, I haven't. I haven't.
I know a lot of people have been posting a lot,
so I wonder if like you've, uh,
you've reached out to anybody?
No. Are you just too
busy Probably to take on more work?
That's usually the case. It's
Like, well, well, if I see a one that that can,
that can pay for both clients actually,
but now Okay, three.
Yeah, With the three was too much. It was too much.
I was struggling with three people.
Three, one was part-time was fulltime
because so much so to cut you loose.
For sure. Man. I totally get it. Asim. What's up man?
Can you hear me?
Yeah. Zone. How are you?
I'm fine. How, how are finals?
It is, it is, uh, I don't know.
It is gonna happen in like a month or so.
So yeah, still time.
Oh, you're still preparing? Yeah. Nice. Um, how's it,
I'm not taking any work.
That's, that's, that's, that's all.
You're just not taking any work right now. Yeah.
That's smart to just kind of
focus on one thing at a time, right?
Yeah. Focusing on getting the exam mindset right now.
Yeah. How, how is that
for you shifting from school to work?
I feel like it's very, very different.
Yeah. It's kind of hard sometimes you get stressed out.
Uh, like last month it was holidays, but still I was working
and it was kind of stressful,
but it becomes even harder when the exams, uh, come
around like the internals and the finals.
So yeah, it's kind of hard, but I'm managing.
You're managing, that's good.
Yeah, I think when I was in school I couldn't do,
I would either just not end up doing any schoolwork.
I would just fail. That was my problem.
But if you're able to balance both, you have the discipline,
then more power to you.
That's awesome. Sam, are you at school?
Yeah. It's a big one for me. 2024.
I'm going through my final exam.
That'll be by, yeah, next year. Exams two.
You guys have exams too. Wow. It's so funny.
Um, well, awesome, man. Thanks for jumping on today, guys.
Um, it'll be a short one today,
but I definitely want to help you guys out
in any way possible.
Um, Sam, I saw that you had posted a recent video.
Um, yeah, for, for some revision requests,
and I had a look at it and it was actually pretty good.
Um, I assumed Were you able to check it out?
Actually, I, I haven't been much active
in the community lately.
No, it's all good. All good.
Um, is this, Sam, is this something you wanted
to maybe go over or get any pointers on?
Or did you already send this to client?
Yeah, already send this to client. Yeah.
Were they happy with it? They were so excited about it.
Um, yeah,
You guys, I was a nice critic actually,
so I still have a lot to ally with, sounds like.
And yeah, and it wasn't only that hook.
There were other hooks too. So that was one outta six hooks.
One outta six hooks. Nice. Yeah.
Um, what's your process of,
of like choosing hooks?
Um, based on the copyright
on the, the script?
Based on the script? Yeah.
I try to pick action points, especially when
what the script is describing something I just get
a creep that kind of grabbing their attention on.
Then also kind of like
telling what the script is.
So are you guys, um, are you guys using any spy tools
by chance to look up different hook ideas?
How about you assume No,
Actually no. Right now I'm
just focused on graphic design
and not the creative or the as spot.
So yeah, I've nail nailed down the, uh, design theories.
So still, uh, doing the tools
and everything, uh, we still need a lot of practice.
Got it. Um, cool.
We'll, we'll circle back to that in a second
and we'll let Sam finish.
But, um, yeah, Sam, do you have access to like a magic brief
or foreplay by chance?
Yeah, I do have access to for play.
You do? Yeah. Yeah.
Awesome. Awesome.
Yeah, I think that's been super helpful for me
to get inspiration for like different editing styles is just
looking at, looking at other videos
and replicating similar, just similar things.
Obviously. I think in the game,
everyone is just basically copying from everybody.
Yeah. It's literally, it's the same in ads
in the ad world, it's always been this way.
It's been the same, it's in the same for like YouTube.
Uh, it's same for like organic.
Um, everyone is just always copying somebody.
So like nothing is really original, right?
Every, you're just building off of someone else's idea
and you're expanding on that.
So I think that's where the originality comes in,
in creating your own, um, is,
is like leveraging someone else's idea
and then building on top of it, making it better.
Um, so it's like a pizza.
It's like, okay, like I adding your own,
adding your own dishes to it or your own toppings to it.
Um, that's always been my thing, but, uh,
but yeah, I think graphic design is seem,
is, is, is interesting.
Sorry, I wasn't able to get back to you on, um, some
of those like resources.
'cause I just haven't had any, I don't know,
I don't think I have much like design resources,
but I can definitely give you some pointers on how I,
how I learned I guess.
Um, but yeah, what are you currently experiencing
with the graphic design stuff?
So, yeah, no problem with the resources.
I can easily find them on foreplay. Mm-Hmm.
Uh, so what I, what I've found is that I need
to focus on the principles and the tools
and mainly the techniques.
Um, I've kind of, uh, find found ways to do all that,
but, um, some of your insights will be grateful.
Definitely. Um, Sam, it's good to see your face, man.
I love, um, loving the, uh, the background.
Is it like purple,
Blue, Blue? That looks nice, man.
Yeah. Looks my,
Looks sick, bro.
Um, yeah, I think,
I think the biggest thing for graphic design
and, and Sam lemme know.
Do you do any graphic design yourself?
No, Just video editing.
I'm not for graphic. Um, I think one
of the biggest things is like color balance
and, um, proportions as well as typography.
I think like, those are when, when you're designing anything
in as an image, it's like, it, it should be balanced.
Um, I don't know if there's like a certain law to that,
but for me it's always like,
even spacing on everything.
Like think of everything in grids.
Um, you know, just like in video
where it's like you have a four by four grid, it's like,
okay, I'm gonna place this here, this here, this here,
this here, or a nine, no, you know, a three, uh, nine
by nine grid and just kind of like, follow that,
um, that golden rule, so to speak.
Um, I, I really, when you can start transitioning,
like the spacing and stuff really matters when you do like
web design, right?
So like in web design, you,
there's a thing called padding.
Have you heard of it? Like, it's the spacing in
between like the blocks.
Um, and so I feel like with good graphic design,
you should have very clear spacing
and between every element, you know, in video,
like you can just like slap things together.
You know, you could put like social proof
here, you could put a thing here.
It's like no one's really, no one really caress, you know,
it does, there's no like principles,
but when you're looking at, let's say, okay, I'll use this
'cause this is only happens is a tub of lotion,
right by my desk.
That's fine because I, I have dry hands of course.
But one of the things that has,
like when I became a graphic designer is I started looking
at every design that was around me.
Billboards, tv, magazines, labels, all of it.
And you start to develop the patterns, um,
between all the designs and then,
and the color choices, right?
Color complimentary,
complimentary colors is gonna be such a big
part in graphic design as well.
So your font choice, your spacing, your colors
is like probably the basics.
And then, um, trying to highlight
the most important aspects in the design that, that the,
that I needs to read, right?
Because you can take a block of text, like a paragraph,
and you know, if you show that a paragraph to somebody,
it's really hard to discern like what's,
what's valuable information or not, right?
So as a designer, your job is to take something that's like
busy and then start to either highlight
or diminish certain elements
that the user should pay, um, pay attention to.
So in this example, new and improved is red, right?
And just like this could be in the same concept of design,
designing ads, designing websites, anything.
It's like, okay, obviously the brand wanted this
to be featured new and improved.
So it's in bright red, right?
Then if you can read even closer,
there's actually social proofer here,
or like, actually authority.
It says, number one,
dermatologists recommended facial skincare brand.
So they, you have to remember, we read from like
left to right, at least most places left to right,
bottom down, right?
We're not reading from the bottom up.
So you're gonna be placing the most in most important
information at the top.
And then kind of working your way down.
So up here you have new and improved,
and at the very bottom you have the weight,
which is not really like valuable information, right?
But it still needs to be there.
So as you can tell, it goes new
and improved, which is almost like, maybe like an offer,
like something like it's,
it's, it's a grabbing your attention.
This is your hook, this is your scroll stopper, right?
The next one is your social proof or your authority.
Number one dermatologist recommended. Okay, great.
Now you have the product introduction.
You have Cetaphil as you know, introducing Cetaphil,
and then now you have the benefits and features right there.
Boom. Moisturizing cream, that's the feature.
And then for very dry skin sensitive skin, right? Benefit.
Oh yeah, here's another benefit.
Hydrates for 48 hours and fully restores skin barrier.
That is a strong, strong benefit.
Um, and yeah, and then it has like some seals right here.
Five skin sensitivity. But there you go.
This is like, this is one
of the biggest things I've realized from d um,
designing landing pages, image ads and websites
and videos, is they all follow the exact same
process from top to bottom.
Importance, level of importance.
You have your hook, you have a grab attention,
and then you work your way down.
So, n video, right? It's left to right, you have a timeline.
We're, we're working on this timeline, right?
Boom, boom, boom. In image is you're, and,
and websites are working from top to bottom.
Yep, exactly. So websites as well,
I don't know if you've heard of it, but it's called top
of the fold, which is basically what your screen
can see on a website without scrolling.
And this is just,
this is the most important part of your website.
It's equivalent to your scroll stopper. First three seconds.
Same thing as, um, your, sorry, I just forgot the name.
I just said, uh, top of fold.
So fold meaning, you know, it's like the bottom of your,
your, your screen.
So the user has three seconds to decide, three
to five seconds to decide.
The first thing that they're gonna read on any type
of website or any type of image ad is what?
Asim, can you answer that?
Sorry, I missed that. Can you repeat it?
The first thing that anyone is going to read
and notice on a website or an image ad is what
Another focal point?
Maybe the, uh, the product.
Typically it's going to be the headline. Oh.
So you're gonna notice,
and let's just break down really quick.
'cause graphic design and web
design are pretty much the same thing.
So, um,
let me pull up some good landing pages.
Okay. I found this really awesome landing
page the other day.
Um, so when I say above the fold on typically,
'cause I have a super large, um, screen, this is
what you're gonna see, right?
Um, and the first thing that notices like that you notice is
probably this Christmas sale right here, right?
Because they're pushing this offer.
But this is what's screaming at you right now.
Discount 70% off last chance.
You, you probably will notice this as well.
The imagery image is going
to make a huge difference as well.
But you're gonna be focusing on these two elements.
And as you can tell, like they're keeping it very simple in
terms of your focal point
and like the mount of text on screen, um, as well
as the color contrast of the call to action buttons.
So this green
and this orange are like a perfect
complimentary to each other.
Like these are, that's kind of like what you're looking
for in any type of image.
Ad or web design is a, is a strong
visual contrast.
One of my mentors back in the day, he told me,
anytime you're designing something, you want to like,
almost like move back really far away from it.
Like make it really small and then tell,
and then be like, okay, show me where the, where the call
to action is and if it's really small,
but if it's well designed, you'll,
you'll know where the call to action is.
Right? Can you guys tell me what color it is?
Orange? Yep, exactly.
Uh, so I,
So just like in video, just like in design,
you are persuading someone to take action.
You're persuading someone, you're not doing it
through video, you're doing it through text,
and you're doing it through imagery.
And so you're design has to accomplish those things.
One, it has to get attention. Number two has to persuade.
Number three, it has to do some sort of call
to action, right?
So Asim, are you following along? Is this helpful?
Uh, this is kind of helpful.
So what I've found is that layer layout
and composition is the final thing that we have to focus on,
and it incorporates everything.
Mm-Hmm. And what you,
what you have said also falls in line with that.
So yeah, the tips are really great.
Awesome. Now, let me ask you this.
What type of like designs are you trying to make?
Are you're trying to make ads? Are you trying to make like,
graphics for like what Yeah.
What type of graphics are you making?
So yeah, mainly statics ads.
Uh, static ads similar to what we did, uh,
I don't know, maybe a month ago.
Mm-Hmm. Yeah.
So I'm focusing on, uh, nailing that down first
and then move on to creative strategy
and then maybe media buying
and maybe marketing is, it's gonna be a,
a long path, I guess.
That's awesome, man. Noel,
I think they all build on, on top of each other.
Yeah. And I'm, I'm trying to, um, like, uh,
build up a completely a set of complimentary skills, so, so
that I can, you know, increase my
value, uh, in, in the long term.
I love it. I think my, yeah,
that brings up a really good point is, um, I think one
of my goals, I think for ads Orx
and then everybody part of the community over the next like
few years is to, um, teach
ultimately like creative entrepreneurship to, uh,
to creators, to creatives.
So, you know, as like, similar to me, I started off
as a graphic designer, so that was my first skill, um,
learning how to design Photoshop,
and then learning how to basically design websites in
Photoshop and then, you know, and then go there.
So I, I learned, I did that for five years.
So five years of just, just graphic design
and basically copying landing pages
over and over again, right?
So after that is when I learned video.
Um, actually after that is when I learned, um, media buying
and then, and then I jumped into video.
So I kind of like did both.
But the point is, they were step-by-step things that I had
to learn in order to get to that next stage
of like, my development.
But ultimately, I think the goal is for any type of creative
is to be able to either
create your own agency, create your own product, um,
and be your own boss, you know what I mean?
Like, and drive your own traffic
and like, do all the things that, um, any,
any business owner can do.
'cause I, I fully believe that creative people have
this crazy emerging opportunity in the world
to, to, like, I guess what I'm trying
to say is like, there wasn't a path for creatives before,
and now there is, right?
Creative is like, so in demand in all aspects,
like social media, websites, like ads,
YouTube, everything we see, bro,
it's freaking, it's it's video.
You know, everything we see is video and images, like,
and so there's more and more like requirements for this.
And then like people, people
who are not creative are gonna be like left behind
because like, they don't have these
skills and they don't have these gifts.
So they're like relying on things like AI
and stuff to like generate that for them.
But creative people are gonna just
be creative no matter what.
So I do believe it's a game of skill acquisition,
leveling yourself up, um,
and then always having creativity as like the foundation.
And then eventually,
I guess it seemed the way I see you potentially going is
you'll probably maybe like build your own brand one day
because you'll have all this marketing knowledge, um, or,
or sell your own products one day
or partner up with somebody
who maybe is a little bit more analytical on some degree,
and then you handle all the creative aspects
and then you have a 50 50 relationship, uh, in the business.
That's kind of the way it's been for me.
Like in the past I've, I've partnered up with like,
I was always the creative guy,
and then I had other partners who did like logistics
and fulfillment and all this stuff that I didn't wanna do.
'cause that's super boring to me.
So anyways, I think you're on the right path, bro.
Um, but I,
let's just go over some of these designs in, um,
in magic brief, just so we can kind of see some,
some designs and break 'em down for you.
But you're gonna see, you're gonna see a big
pattern here, right?
Like, I think one of the, um, important things
to recognize in any image ad is like what stood out,
you know, and then you kind of break that down.
Um, so there's obviously a, a format very similar to like
how we do video ads, right?
Guys, you know, this is a testimonial format,
this is like a product feature format.
This is, um, an offer,
this is a discount, right?
There's, there's all these different
formats that we can follow.
And then from there, then it gives us
an area to focus on.
Um, like this is a press feature.
My best tip for you, Asim,
and this is what I did, is I traced video, I traced images,
do, do you know what I mean by that?
Yeah. Yeah. So break down everything
and learning from them.
So we watch engineering, I guess.
So literally, okay, do you remember when we were kids,
like in like elementary school, you would like take a piece
of paper and then you would put, you know, your,
you have like a image
and then you put a piece of paper on top of it
and then you draw, outline you out. You would outline it.
Yeah. Do you ever do that?
Yeah, you do the exact same thing.
I do the exact same thing with images and video.
So I'm gonna save this video and then I can recreate it
because like I, now I know the framework.
Um, because here's the thing, I didn't learn necessarily,
like the theories of how to design like
the proper proportions, da da, I didn't go to school for it.
Let's be real. I just said, f**k it, I'm gonna go in there
and I'm just gonna try to copy it.
And then you copy it enough times
and then eventually you figure it out.
You're like, oh, there's a pattern here, right?
So here's my first layer,
and now all I do, I just start like editing over it, right?
This is my copy.
And now I have this like, winning framework
that I don't need to like reinvent from the beginning.
This is,
and I used to do this for full websites,
like full landing pages that are like super long.
Um, obviously wouldn't make it like exact,
but like I would just screenshot the whole thing
and then I would go in there
and I would just start making it my own.
Um, now one thing you can do with this is like, okay,
if you don't want to cheat, like, like that,
just add a layer over it, like a shape,
and then you can just slowly kind
of build it like this if you want.
Um, and kind of like peek at it. This is kind of what I do.
Sometimes I'll just like peek at it.
Um, but yeah, like, it, it doesn't need
to get like super complicated.
Um, I,
unless you're like a theory guy, like you,
like you like knowing the theories of stuff,
which it sounds like you kind, you do.
'cause it, it's better for your learning and understanding.
Yeah, this tip is like really amazing and
or absolutely essential.
Uh, but I think that, uh, a little bit
of theory will help you like, uh,
break down the ads much, uh, easily.
Uh, that's what I think. I don't know.
Everyone think like that, but yeah, that's what I think
Knowing the theory will help you analyze
the ads better. Is that what you said?
Yeah. Analyze and break down the ad.
Like, uh, I found that layout
and competition is the, uh, main thing in the design.
Mm-Hmm. And to be able to break down other ads, uh, uh,
might help me to, you know, like, uh,
create converting ads again and again.
Uh, that's what I think. I don't know if, if,
if my thought is, uh, right or wrong,
but yeah, that's what I, that's, that's my opinion.
So composition is gonna be one thing, 100%,
but it's not gonna be everything, right?
Yeah. I think, um, it's all of the elements together, right?
So if you, if we take video for example, you know,
it's not, you know, it's not just the text,
it's not just the music, it's not just it, you know
how long the video is.
It's the entire thing, right?
It's the entire emotional experience in the video that like
maybe can persuade somebody, you know?
And, and, and there's gonna be different
elements that persuade people.
It's not just one, um, it's not just one part of the video.
One part of the video can resonate
with somebody else, you know what I mean?
It's, it's subjective in that way
and you'll never know exactly what it is
unless you did like a perfect study for it.
Now the good thing with images though, is there are things
like, like heat maps.
Have you heard of heat maps?
Uh, no. It's the first time.
Oh, really? Okay. So website.
So you can basically, like, let's say you have a website
and you have, um, a heat map installed on it,
you can see the behavior of somebody
who's looking at your website.
So this is what's very, very powerful with image, um,
and web design and any type of graphic design is like,
you can see where people are either clicking
or where their mouse is going.
'cause where their mouse goes is
where their eyeballs go, right?
And you'll see,
and especially in design, like when you split test
somebody who's looking at the text versus not looking,
there's gonna be a, a dramatic difference in like,
in the click-through rate or like the Yeah,
the overall conversion on the page.
Um, so in essence, like
you can kind of think of, of, of this as composition,
but you can also think of it as like, okay, well
what is the message that people are resonating with?
Is it the offer that people are resonating with?
So I think there's a lot
of good composition in these ads, right?
So when we talk about composition, I think like
how it is composed, right?
This is like quote,
Yeah. Basically
how, how the elements are orange,
Exactly. How
the elements are arranged.
That's a perfect way of saying it.
Now, how the elements are arranged is definitely one thing.
And the second thing is how they're spoken to,
how are they spoken to the person, right?
Um, I know in the past I've seen ads
that are composed very, very, very beautifully,
but they don't convert as well as another one.
Um, because the messaging was better.
So you can split test the same image
with a different headline,
and they'll, they'll produce different results.
Same composition, right?
And then that's, that's where you can really determine
what's moving the needle forward.
Because at the end of the day, I believe
that the most strongest element that you have to convince
and persuade someone is what you say.
So what's being said in the ad, you know, on a text format
and what is being like emoted in a video?
You know? Um, sometimes like
you can say all the right things in a video,
but if the actor or,
or like the person in the video doesn't seem believable,
like it's not gonna, it's just not gonna convert.
So it's very, it's very nuanced, right?
You're dealing with human psychology at the end of the day.
Um, and you can make some of these, uh,
like generalization statements, but composition
and messaging is going to be probably the biggest things.
Um, so don't ever exclude that from your design.
Um, so copywriting,
when I first started designing, I wasn't a copywriter.
Like I didn't really, and I'm still not like an,
I'm not an amazing copywriter.
Um, here's a, here's a good example of like good copy
plus good composition, right?
Wrap up, Billy, this holiday.
The only razor on their wishlist.
Like that's, that's like, I think the difference
between photos and video is that like,
just like when you take a regular photo, um,
you have one chance, you have a still, you have one frame,
versus a video is like 30 seconds, right?
You have one frame to make or break. Someone's like choice.
Uh, and if you do a good job, like then you win.
But I think whoever wrote this put a lot of thought into it.
The only razor on their wishlist, I think like it's a,
it's a smart piece of copy.
Because let's say you remove this,
the only razor on their wishlist,
and you just had the image, this thing wouldn't sell nearly
as well, right?
Yeah, obviously.
Yeah. But, but sometimes images, just images,
like if the image is composed in a really, like,
persuasive way, like someone holding the razor, you know,
and then like a bag of money
or something like that, you know, it kind of like maybe
can insinuate what the message is,
but if you added a message, it's like,
never pay hundreds of dollars for razors.
Again. It's like, oh, oh, that's what they're trying to say.
So you want, you wanna be able to transfer that message
as best as possible
and as clear as possible to the other side.
And adding to that, so when I was trying to find videos
to learn on YouTube, uh,
what I came across was visual messaging in graphic design.
And, uh, but, uh, in the, in, uh, on foreplay
and, uh, on ad libraries, I,
I haven't really found a visual
messaging being used too much.
So what's your opinion on that?
Can you go into visual messaging a little bit more?
I'm not sure if I understand what that means.
So actually using the, uh,
visual elements rather than the text
or the copy, uh, using the visual elements
to convey the message, uh, like for in case of a coffee,
uh, rather than just saying that this coffee is, uh,
will not have any side effects
or will help you wake up early in the morning.
Uh, the showing, uh, like a cop with, uh,
the elements of alarm clock.
Like there was an example in video.
So, so there, there is a coffee cup
and there's some elements of the alarm clock.
So using those elements, the messages
that it'll help you wake up early in the
morning. So there's something like that.
Yeah. Yes.
I think, um, and you called it like visual messaging?
Uh, it is not something I told, uh, it was said in the,
it was said in the video that
Tom was being used in the video.
I think, yeah, I think any like, subtle cues,
'cause it really taps into your subconscious, right?
Like, you may not realize it,
but like some of these images have like very, you know,
very subconscious positioning
and like it, let's say if it was coffee,
it's like never be late again, would be the headline.
And then you have coffee, someone like drinking coffee
and then you have like someone with their
watch, like looking at the time.
Mm-hmm, right? It's like late time coffee meet,
you make the association, it's relatable.
Um, so it's really true when they say like, an image
is like a thousand words, right?
You're, you're trying to not make it overly stuffed
with a bunch of elements.
You're trying to make it clear and concise, um,
and still get the point across
because in, let's say a video, you can tell a whole script.
You can, you can talk about that
for five minutes if you want to, or 10 minutes.
Um, but an image you have with that one, one choice.
So when testing images, you can obviously test
that visual imagery as well as the headline.
Which one is gonna resonate better, right?
So in the ab tests, um, so I think testing is a lot easier
for images than it is for video
'cause you only have a few elements to test.
Sam, anything you want to add to that, bro?
Uh, so going a little bit off topic.
So it's about messaging, uh, it's the definition I've,
uh, come up with.
So what I've come up with is that messaging is, uh,
just about, uh, telling your idea or your opinion or,
or providing information, uh,
about your products to the customers.
That's the simplest, uh, definition
that I could come up with to understand it.
So what do you think about that definition?
Say it one more time. Uh, messaging is just about, uh,
providing the information about your products,
about the features, uh, or, uh,
or about any kinds of benefit, uh,
about your products to the customers.
That's the simplest form of
simplest definition that I could come up
with. So what do you mean about that?
Yeah, I would say in a nutshell, that's what it is.
It's like how are you, how you speak to the customer
and who you're speaking to?
What are you speaking about?
Yeah, I think it's like who, who, what, who, what, why?
Like, it's, it's using the framework of, it's called,
so Socratic selling, I don't know if you've heard of it.
Socratic selling or questioning.
Oh, it's the first time. Um, okay,
what is Socratic questioning?
Socratic questioning is a method of inquiry that seeks
to explore complex ideas, concepts, please,
by asking questions that challenge assumptions,
clarify meeting and reveal underlying principles.
Um, one of the things, it's like, who am I talking to?
Like, I, it's like, who, what, when, where, how, why?
Like, it's those standard questions that for me,
allow me to craft a better message to the ideal person.
So that message is very clear and concise.
Messaging should be clear and concise.
And that could be, you know, in that, in that one, in
that example, the only razor on their wishlist,
it's like, that's the messaging.
Who is that? Who are we talking to?
Um, there, there, there, there's a lot
to unpack in that messaging, right?
So let me just go back there really quick.
The only razor, damn,
I lost it on their wishlist.
They're implying there as in who,
like, women there, I think this,
this messaging could be towards men.
Um, I could be wrong,
but like, they could be speaking, they could be like trying
to message men that, hey, get this for your wife.
Um, I don't know. What do you guys think?
Messaging. 'cause it could be a little unclear
here if you're not sure.
Yeah, it's, we can't tell if it's for women or men. I,
Okay, I gotta go. Oh
snap. I gotta take my kids to school.
All right guys, I gotta head out. Okay. I'm late.
Sorry about that. I'll let, I'll share the recording later.
It, it was a nice chat. Thank you. See you guys. Bye.
Okay, bye.